<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.7.4">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-03-19T10:00:45-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Bread Gang</title><subtitle>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Rules of Icing (🍞 Edition)</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/icing/2019/03/18/icing-rules.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Rules of Icing (🍞 Edition)" /><published>2019-03-18T13:54:59-04:00</published><updated>2019-03-18T13:54:59-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/icing/2019/03/18/icing-rules</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/icing/2019/03/18/icing-rules.html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;icing&quot;&gt;Icing&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;history&quot;&gt;History&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In ancient Greek history, King Sisyphus was made to roll a huge boulder endlessly up a steep hill. The maddening nature of the punishment was reserved for King Sisyphus due to his hubristic belief that his cleverness surpassed that of Zeus himself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zeus accordingly displayed his own cleverness by enchanting the boulder into rolling away from King Sisyphus before he reached the top, which ended up consigning Sisyphus to an eternity of useless efforts and unending frustration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Little is it known that after 3000 years King Sisyphus was able to reach the top of the mountain. There he found a Smirnoff Ice waiting for him placed by Zeus. Making Sisyphus the first in history to be iced and Zeus the almighty bro.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;rules&quot;&gt;Rules&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;getting-iced&quot;&gt;Getting Iced&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The icee has to do it to themselves (i.e an action that reveals the ice. For example opening a door and see the ice).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;If an individual gets iced and no one is around to witness it they must live-stream it on Facebook.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;If you refuse to take the ice you will be shunned and booed for 2 days.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;ice-block&quot;&gt;Ice Block&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;An individual can “ICE BLOCK” an ice if they have and ice in arms reach.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;This can stack and 1L are legal.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A reverse Uno card can be used but it needs to be from a real Uno pack and must be burnt after use.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;void&quot;&gt;Void&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;An individual can void and ice if they claim the location of the ice before the ice is revealed.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;If the claim is valid the icer gets iced.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;If
the claim is wrong the claimer must buy an ice or a drink of 345 ml and chug it in at least 2 seconds if it is not alcoholic.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;special-icing-forms&quot;&gt;Special Icing Forms&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The following drinks are included in icing:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Smirnoff Ice 1L&lt;/strong&gt;: can be used if you ice the individual gets Iced 3 times in a row.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;del&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GODS NECTAR&lt;/strong&gt; (PABST): is considered low tier but can still be used. If an individual gets Pabst’d they must shotgun it.&lt;/del&gt; PBR IS ILLEGAL&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Yeethanize&lt;/strong&gt;: The use of Delirium is highly respected as it is a rare boi. Limit of 5 per day.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;deferred-ices&quot;&gt;Deferred Ices&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The icee and ask the icer to defer the ice for 6 hours. The icer must agree to these conditions or it must be taken on the spot.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</content><author><name>Samuel Catherasoo</name><email>sam111jc@gmail.com</email></author><summary type="html">Icing</summary></entry></feed>